ustr.gov 2001-06-02

# USTR - Privacy Statement

## Office of the  
United States Trade Representative:  
Privacy Statement

* * *

**_Privacy and Security Statement_**

Thank you for visiting the website of the Office of the United States Trade Representative (USTR). USTR respects your privacy. This is how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our website. The information we receive depends upon what you do when visiting our site.

**We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you specifically and knowingly choose to provide such information to us.**

_If you visit our site to read or download information, such as career opportunities or press releases, we collect and store **only** the following information about you:_  

  * The name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account).
  * The date and time you access our site.
  * The Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site.
  * The browser type and operating system version you used to access our site.

_If you identify yourself by sending personal information:_  
You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example your mailing address, in an electronic or postal mail message in which you request information or provide information that warrants supervisory or other attention. Personal information collected in this manner is used solely for responding to the original message.

**For site management** , information from both categories may be collected for statistical purposes. This Government computer system uses software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.

**For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users** , this Government computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

* * *

Contact @ USTR - September 2000
